

EDUCATION

National Forensic July 2019 Sciences University to Current M.Sc. Cyber Security 2021

Gujarat Technological July 2014 to University July 2018

B.e Computer Engineering 2018

SUMMARY

Skilled Cyber Security Analyst with proficient and thorough expertise and good understanding of information technology. specialized in proactive monitoring of digital assets using SIEM (Splunk). Able to use various security tools to perform log analysis and to identify suspicious activity. Also have working experience as technical consultant so can easily deal with people.

SKILLS

TOOLS: Metasploit, Nmap, Burpsuite, Autopsy, Maltego, Wireshark, Nessus, Shodan, Splunnk, Mobilyzer Forenisc Toolkit, FTK **TECHNOLOGY:** Vmware, Virtual box, Azure Cloud Computing, Google cloud Platform, Kali Linux, Windows, Ubuntu **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES:** Python, C programming, C++ Programming, Bash Scripting, HTML,CSS

EMPLOYMENT

COLGATE-PALMOLIVE

Cyber Security Intern

Jan. 2021 to Current

Worked in SOC to help identify loopholes, malwares and any suspicious activities. Also worked on Threat-intel to provide a better security perspective.

REESS GMBH

Technical Consultant

June 2018 to Dec. 2018

Provided deep insights to technical knowledge base to the clients, worked on clients requirements. Also was a part of Research group to help create workshop contents

PROJECTS

ACTIVE DIRECTORY PENTESTING

Jan. 2021 to Current

Working on Active Directory pretesting, where in i created a active directory with domain controller and users and tried several ways a attacker can use to attack the domain.

DOCKER CONTAINER SECURITY

June 2020 to Dec. 2020

Conducted Penetration Testing of docker container by deploying it onto local system and tried every possible way a attacker can use to breach into containers.

JUICE JACKING Dec. 2019 to May 2020

Juice jacking was a attacker based project, where-in iot device was used to grab data of victims from public places where charging station are available.

ONLINE COMIC BOOKS 2016 to 2018

Online comic books is a php and ionic based webapp that allowed creators to create comic books online and share the same within the community.

VOLUNTEERING

MICROSOFT · Microsoft Student Partner

June 2017 to June 2018

Served as Microsoft Student Partner as well as Microsoft student learn ambassador to promote new tools and technology to peers as well as colleges around Gujarat.

GIRLSCRIPT · Chapter Lead Ahmedabad

Apr. 2017 to Jan. 2018

Served as a Chapter lead for GirlScript foundation (NGO promoting women in tech) for a period of 10+months. The major role performed during this period included deliverables of tech talks and helping the core team for the India Summit held in Jan 2018